{
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 0,
      "question": "незграбний",
      "answer": "ungeschickt",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "interval": 0,
      "nextReview": 0,
      "repCount": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "fleißig",
      "answer": "unermüdlich",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "interval": 0,
      "nextReview": 0,
      "repCount":  0
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "смачний",
      "answer": "köstlich",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "interval": 0,
      "nextReview": 0,
      "repCount":  0
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "запалювати",
      "answer": "anzünden",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "interval": 0,
      "nextReview": 0,
      "repCount":  0
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "луг",
      "answer": "Die Wiese",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "interval": 0,
      "nextReview": 0,
      "repCount":  0
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Підкреслювати, виділяти",
      "answer": "unterstreichen",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "interval": 0,
      "nextReview": 0,
      "repCount":  0
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Обдарованість, талант",
      "answer": "Die Begabung",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "interval": 0,
      "nextReview": 0,
      "repCount":  0
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Провірка, огляд",
      "answer": "Die Durchsicht",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "interval": 0,
      "nextReview": 0,
      "repCount":  0
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Основний, базовий",
      "answer": "grundlegend",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "interval": 0,
      "nextReview": 0,
      "repCount":  0
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Помста",
      "answer": "Die Rache",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "interval": 0,
      "nextReview": 0,
      "repCount":  0
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Спостерігати",
      "answer": "zusehen",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "interval": 0,
      "nextReview": 0,
      "repCount":  0
    }
  ]
}
